Guide to the Stanford University, Office of Summer Session, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Office of Summer Session, records
1960-1970
SC0079
Stanford University. Office of Summer Session.
4.5 Linear feet
Records of the Director's Office, including budget files, correspondence and mimeographed information sheets, questionnaires sent to summer shool students in order to evaluate the program, and files regarding the Association of University Summer Sessions.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfer, Office of Summer Session, 1970.
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use.
Description of the Collection
Records of the Director's Office, including budget files, correspondence and mimeographed information sheets, questionnaires sent to summer shool students in order to evaluate the program, and files regarding the Association of University Summer Sessions.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Office of Summer Session.; Universities and colleges--Administration.
Collection Contents
- Records
  - Budget General, 1961-1963 (Box 1)
  - Budget Commitments, 1963-1964 (Box 1)
  - Budget General, 1963-1964 (Box 1)
  - Budget Commitments, 1964-1965 (Box 1)
  - Budget General, 1964-1965 (Box 1)
  - Budget Commitments, 1965-1966 (Box 1)
  - Budget General, 1965-1966 (Box 1)
  - Expenditures for Department Brochures, 1966 (Box 1)
  - New Basic Travel Schedule, 1965-1966 (Box 1)
  - Travel Commitments, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Budget Commitments, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - Department Brochure Expenses, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - Budget Commitments, 1967-1968 (Box 1)
  - Departmental Brochure Expenses, 1967-1968 (Box 1)
  - Budget General, 1968-1970 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid, 1964-1965 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid, 1965-1966 (Box 1)
  - Tuition, 1965-1966 (Box 1)
  - Enrollment, 1961-1963 (Box 1)
  - Enrollment: Course Consumption (Figures for President's Report), 1962-1963 (Box 1)
  - Enrollment Tables (Registrar's Office Report), 1962-1963 (Box 1)
  - Enrollment Tables, 1962-1963 (Box 1)
  - Enrollment, 1963-1964 (Box 1)
  - Enrollment, 1964-1965 (Box 1)
  - Course Comparisons: Ten Students or Less, 1961-1965 (Box 1)
  - Enrollment, 1965-1966 (Box 1)
  - Enrollment, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
  - Statistics on Faculty and Courses, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Appointments for Summer "A-L", 1968 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Appointments for Summer "M-Z", 1968 (Box 1)
  - Visiting Faculty, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Leaves of Absence (Faculty), 1964-1965 (Box 1)
  - Leaves of Absence (Faculty), 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Mailing List and Summer Faculty Party, 1965-1966 (Box 1)
  - Future Programs, Undated (Box 1)
  - Director's Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Committee, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Provost's Office, Undated (Box 1)
  - Dr E. Howard Brooks, Undated (Box 1)
  - Timothy Wirth, Undated (Box 1)
  - American History, Institute of (Coe), Undated (Box 2)
  - Business - Graduate School of, Undated (Box 2)
  - East Asian Studies, 1960 (Box 2)
  - East Asian Studies, 1961-1963 (Box 2)
  - Education: Pre-College Guidance and College Admissions, Undated (Box 2)
  - School of Education, Undated (Box 2)
  - Engineering-General, Undated (Box 2)
  - Geography, Undated (Box 2)
  - Geology, Undated (Box 2)
  - Hoover Institution, Undated (Box 2)
  - International Center (Bechtel) English Programs, Undated (Box 2)
  - H. and S. Latin American Studies, Undated (Box 2)
  - Law, School of, Undated (Box 2)
  - H. and S. Mathematics, Undated (Box 2)
  - Men's Physical Education, Undated (Box 2)
  - Speech Pathology, Undated (Box 2)
  - Western Civilization, Undated (Box 2)
  - Women's Physical Education, Undated (Box 2)
  - Graduate Special Courses, Undated (Box 2)
  - Housing and Residences, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
  - Residences and Food Service, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Letter of Information, Undated (Box 2)
  - Summer School Bulletin: Promotional Information, 1968-1970 (Box 2)
  - Summer School Bulletin, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Registration Day, Undated (Box 2)
  - Calendar, Undated (Box 2)
  - Time Schedule, Undated (Box 2)
  - Student Privilege Cards, Undated (Box 2)
  - Special Arrangements, Undated (Box 2)
  - Promotional Material: Ads, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - Brochures by Stanford: former years, Undated (Box 2)
  - Association of Summer School Deans and Directors, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Association of Summer School Deans and Directors, 1963-1964 (Box 2)
  - Deans and Directors of Summer Schools, Western Association, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
  - Association of University Summer Sessions, Meeting Charlottesville, 1969 Oct 14-1? (Box 2)
  - Association of University Summer Sessions, 1965-1969 (Box 2)
  - Newspapers' Prices, Undated (Box 3)
  - Keio-Stanford Exchange Program, 1961-1963 (Box 3)
  - Keio-Stanford Exchange Program, 1963-1964 (Box 3)
  - John Hay Fellows Program, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Keio-Stanford Exchange Program, 1964-1965 (Box 3)
  - John Hay Fellows Program, 1961 (Box 3)
  - John Hay Fellows Program, 1962 (Box 3)
  - John Hay Fellows Program, 1963 (Box 3)
  - John Hay Fellows Program, 1964-1965 (Box 3)
  - National Science Foundation Physics Institute, Undated (Box 3)
  - National Science Foundation Materials Science, Undated (Box 3)
  - National Science Foundation Mathematics-College, Undated (Box 3)
  - National Science Foundation Mathematics-High School, Undated (Box 3)
  - Lisle Fellowships, Undated (Box 3)
  - Shell Merit Fellowship Program, Undated (Box 3)
  - Report on Shell Merit Program, 1962 (Box 3)
  - Report on Shell Merit Program, 1964 (Box 3)
  - Report on Shell Merit Program, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Report on Shell Merit Program, 1967 (Box 3)
  - USAR Conference, 1965-1966 (Box 3)
  - Project Upward Bound, Undated (Box 3)
  - Ford Foundation Seminars in Economics, Undated (Box 3)
  - General Electric Summer Fellowship Program-Economics, Undated (Box 3)
  - Questionnaire II: Stanford Summer School, Undated (Box 3)
  - Questionnaire Preparatory Material, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Questionnaire III, 1969 Oct 31 (Box 3)